<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 22:45:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Markdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/posts/markdown-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 22:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/posts/markdown-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;details&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;summary&gt;Click here to view a list of useful markdown references. Mostly just a reference to help me with future posts, but I figured anyone might get some use out of it. I&#39;ll be updating this with any other cool markdown tricks I find. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;&#xD;&#xA;   &lt;h1 id=&#34;markdown-101&#34;&gt;Markdown 101&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is a live demonstration of what you can achieve with Markdown, the simple and elegant syntax for writing for the web. Everything you see here is written in a plain text &lt;code&gt;.md&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 21:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there! My name is Taylor Martin. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in all things that think, from computers, to people/animals, to &amp;lt;insert 3rd category when discovered&amp;gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have worked in various Information Technology fields since 2010. Knowledge management, IT management, logistics tracking, boundary protection, penetration testing, etc. I&amp;rsquo;m also a big gamer, rock climber, mountain biker, imrov actor, joke teller, and whatever else is my hyper fixation for the week.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But for the most part I just like to learn more about how to make cool stuff do fun things, and share that journey with others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/projects/25-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/projects/25-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Projects worked on:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beginning Webdev in 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/posts/beginners-webdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/posts/beginners-webdev/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s so many things that I wish I would have started sooner. The compounding impacts of picking up skills early can be difficult to grasp until later in life. Learning how to cook a decent meal before my 30s would have compounded into a much broader range of culinary interests. Figuring out how to break through social anxiety and make more friends in my early 20&amp;rsquo;s would have led to me having so many more interesting stories an exchanges in the places I&amp;rsquo;ve lived. Blogging, and, by extension, web development seems like one of those massive missed opportunities to have started far earlier in life. There&amp;rsquo;s so much useful routine in tracking your progress through a project, and there&amp;rsquo;s so much freedom in having just a little corner of the internet to post your random ideas and journeys to be able to show to anyone at any time, or just to have a little diary for yourself to reflect back on. That&amp;rsquo;s my intent with this little corner here, just a simple way for me to work on projects and keep track of what I&amp;rsquo;ve had to learn along the way. That way in a another 10 years, I won&amp;rsquo;t have to think about what the compounding impacts of this journey could have been; I&amp;rsquo;ll get to know them first hand.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/projects/25-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/projects/25-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Projects worked on:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My project space</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/projects/projects-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 21:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-blog/projects/projects-space/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a spot to keep track of anything I put some time into during the month. No time tracking or anything, just a vague measure of how many things I dabble in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
